<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwentyFour</string>
    <string name="game_name_24">24</string>
    <string name="level_select">Level Select</string>
    <string name="timed_trials">Timed Trials</string>
    <string name="endless">Endless</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions_text_1"> In this game, you will be given 4
        different numbers initially from a set of cards. The numbers will be
        from 1 to 13 inclusive. You will try to set up a mathematical
        equation using only arithmetic with all 4 numbers to result in an
        answer of exactly 24. If you get the answer of 24, you win.
        Otherwise, you can try press the reset button to try again. You have
        to click a number before you click a card and before you click the
        2nd card, just like how you would write it in math. Otherwise, this
        program does not work and ignores your request. Attached on the right
        is a Demo that you can try out right now. </string>
    <string name="instructions_text_2"> For this page and all
        other pages, you can use the buttons or press a single key to indicate
        what action you want to perform. If you press \'e\' or \'E\', that
        exits the page if an Exit button exists. In the same manner,
        clicking the Exit button exists that page. You can use \'r\' or
        \'R\' as replacements for the Reset button, or you can just click
        the Reset button. You can also type the operation instead of
        clicking if you prefer. The rest of the buttons must be pressed, and
        cannot be used with the keyboard, because they operate very
        differently. In order to give you the best experience
        possible, those were changed to only buttons. </string>
    <string name="instructions_text_3"> This game has 3 different gamemodes
        along with the demo: Practice mode, with many different levels and
        difficulties that you can try; Timed Trials where you are timed to
        complete 10 different levels within 10 of difficulties \"Casual\"
        and \"Challenging\". If you win on that gamemode, you are added to
        the leaderboard! The last mode is Endless mode, where you can choose
        which difficulty you wish to play at and you can just continuously
        play the game without end. It\'s completely stress-free and can help
        improve your skills before you rush into Timed Trials mode. Good
        luck!</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="demo">Demo</string>
    <string name="is_first_card">This is the first card</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="minus">-</string>
    <string name="multiply">*</string>
    <string name="divide">/</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
</resources>